(Sheldon(behind them):)I don't want to shake
anyone's germy hands.
(Sheldon(behind them):)Explain it to
them, Siebert.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I must confess
(Sheldon(on phone):)I don't understand you,
President Siebert.
(Sheldon(on phone):)First you say you want me
to appear at your fund-raisers,
(Sheldon(on phone):)but now you say
you never want me to go
(Sheldon(on phone):)anywhere near your fund-raisers.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Forgive me, but that sounds
like a mixed message.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Here we go again.
(Sheldon(on phone):)If there's simply
no talking to me,
(Sheldon(on phone):)why did you call?
(Sheldon(on phone):)I'm sorry, someone's
on the other line.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Why don't you see if you
can organize your thoughts,
(Sheldon(on phone):)and we'll try again later.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Cooper-Hofstadter residence.
Go for Cooper.
Good morning, Mrs. Latham.
Well, yes, of course
I remember you.
A woman well past her prime
seeking to augment
her social status
by doling out her late husband's
ill-gotten gains.
So, how much money
are you going to give me?
I'm not crazy--
my mother had me tested.